A comedy about the young at heart.
Queen Bees is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Michael Lembeck.
Helen is an independent widow who moves into the Pine Grove Senior Community and
discovers it’s just like high school – full of cliques and flirtatious suitors.
What she initially avoids leads her to exactly what she has been missing:
new friendships and a chance at love again with newcomer Dan.
Helen Wilson, played by Ellen Burstyn.
Dan, played by James Caan.
Margot Clark, played by Ann-Margret.
Jane Poindexter, played by Jane Curtin.
Arthur Lane, played by Christopher Lloyd.
Sally, played by Loretta Devine.
Queen Bees is a 2021 American romantic comedy film directed by Michael Lembeck.
It features an ensemble cast, including Ellen Burstyn, James Caan (in his final film released during his
lifetime), Ann-Margret, Christopher Lloyd, Jane Curtin, Loretta Devine, and Elizabeth Mitchell.
It was released on June 11, 2021, by Gravitas Ventures,
and received mixed reviews from critics.
Screenwriter Donald Martin was nominated for a 2022
Humanitas Prize for his screenplay.
The film explores themes of control freak, forgetful
fire, repairing family connections.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.